Exit Art "Reactions" exhibit collection
Prints & Photographs Division, Library of Congress
- Dreisorner, Jorge
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0575; 1396; 3 rectangular image collages arranged vertically on page; statue of liberty at top www.holycow.de
- Dreisorner, Jorge
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0576; 1393; 3 equal rectangular image collages; Jesus on the cross at top www.holycow.de
- Dreisorner, Jorge
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0577; 1394; Image collage arranged vertically in two segments; (the evil one) www.holycow.de
- Drury, John
  - [Untitled], 0578; 927; Flag house
- Druschell, Bonnie
  - [Untitled], 0579; 720
- DuBasky, Valentina
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0580; 40; Via mail
- Dudham, Keyla
  - [Untitled], 0581; 1545; Face and text
- Dugan Vourakis, Stacie
  - [Untitled], 0583; 3036
- Dunlop, Mac
  - Timepiece, poem; 0584; 2139; I count the grains...
- Dunlop, Mac
  - US/THEM, poem; 0585; 2140; So God says:...
- Dunlop, Mac
  - The number and the names..., poem; 0586; 2141; We drown...
- Dunlop, Mac
  - September 11, 2001, poem; 0587; 2142; Veiled tides...
- Dushanko Dobek, Anne
  - In Memoriam, 0590; 1968; "will you ever..."
- Dushanko Dobek, Anne
  - Crying Flag, 0591; 1969; Elongated flag
- Duwel, Emily
  - Twin Towers Through Blinds, video stills/Photoshop; 0592; 1963
- Duwel, Matthias
  - Smoke No. VI, digitally enhanced watercolor on paper; 0593; 1423; Abstract painting
- E-mael
  - [Untitled], text collage; 0594; 345
- Eade, Michael
  - Washing a Window; Tree of Life, gouache, copper leaf on collaged laser jet; 0595; 678; Illuminated manuscript look
- Eastwood, Martin
  - As Seen From Calvary, 0597; 913
- Ebben, Dean
  - Bird Pile, acrylic, graphite, on handmade paper "Philippine Gampi"; 0598; 1414; Line drawing of wing shape in lower righthand corner of page
- Echevarria-Myers, Anne
  - They were wearing clean underwear, photo; 0599b; 425
- Ecker, Ken
  - 9-13-01, 0600; 1055
- Edelman, Rita
  - 9 1 1, copy and pencil on cardstock; 0601; 666; Strips of paper
- Eder, Melissa
  - In memoriam/Souvenir of NYC, c-print; 0602; 1127; Photograph of a souvenir globe of NYC w/Statue of Liberty
- Edie, Frank
  - [Untitled], collage of mail; 0603; 453
- Efremov, Ivan
  - [Untitled], comp art; 0603b; 3301; Picture with russian text
- Efremov, Ivan
  - [Untitled], comp art; 0603c; 3302; Picture with russian text
- Efremov, Ivan
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0603d; 3303; Space looking
- Efremov, Ivan
  - [Untitled], comp art; 0603e; 3304; Picture with russian text
- Einfinger, Carmen
  - My Scrap Book, mixed media; 0604; 1497; Collaged image and text
- Eins, Stefan
  - [Untitled], 0605; 627; Garbage
- Elaine
  - [Untitled], 0606; 551; 8 of 16
- Eli2
  - [Untitled], 0607; 1480
- Elis, Edward
  - Cultural Evolution, 0609; 131
- Ellis, Loren
  - Beauty Still Stands II, digital image; 0610; 979; Posing nudes in foreground with the statue of liberty and the burning trade center in background lorenellisart.com
- Ellis, Loren
  - Peace II, digital image; 0611; 980; Image of trade center with a globe in foreground lorenellisart.com
- Ellis, Richard
  - The Strangler, digital mixed media on paper; 0612; 1638; Image of man strangling a boy on the left side of the page, buildings in the distance
- Elozua, Raymon & Gingras, Micheline
  - [Untitled], artwork & poem; 0613; 86; By mail; alternate address: Elozua Studios
- EMG
  - [Untitled], 0614; 2260; I appreciate people more...
- Enteles, Cara V.
  - [Untitled], 0616; 430; Text "We will not forget..." and tower collage
- Entour
  - [Untitled], 0617; 32; EXIT ART IS OLD SCHOOL FLAUMA IS THE PRESENT
- Entour
  - [Untitled], 0618; 3101; You are trapped
- Johnson, Melisa Eden
  - Fragment, crayon and cut paper; 0618b; 3251; Red, jagged edges with crayon
- Epes, Maria
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0619; 1078; Image of two damaged towers with verticle text "World Trade Towers" and "September 11, 2001" on either side
- Erenberg, Noah
  - [Untitled], 0620; 320; Collaberation with his mom, Elena Siff "2i nTime"text and photograph
- Erenberg, Sam
  - Habib/Mythologies, photo; 0621; 175
- Ernst, Amy
  - [Untitled], painting/collage; 0622; 340; Forest of Dreams Never Gone, Never Forgotten 9/11/01 New York 2001
- Eskell, Camille
  - Reaction, collage; 0623; 722; Black and white drawing
- Espiritu, Erica
  - [Untitled], photo; 0624; 959; Window and mask
- Estey, Donelle
  - [Untitled], 0625; 570; Snowglobe
- Etienne, Yvan
  - [Untitled], 0626; 266; Print out of RE/ACTION
- Evangeline, Margaret
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0627; 357; Afterburn 2001 wavy drawing
- Evangelista, Anna
  - [Untitled], 0628; 3032; Via email
- Evans, Soraya
  - [Untitled], 0629; 522; East Harlem Tutorial Program
- Ewen, Sam Travis
  - [Untitled], 0630; 298; Stickers that were posted all around the 5 boroughs starting September 18. 1 of 6 "Heal"
- Ewen, Sam Travis
  - [Untitled], 0631; 299; Stickers that were posted all around the 5 boroughs starting September 18. 2 of 6 "For ______ I Will Not Forget. 09.11.01
- Ewen, Sam Travis
  - [Untitled], 0632; 300; Stickers that were posted all around the 5 boroughs starting September 18. 3 of 6 "For Jeremy Glick I Will Not Forget. 09.11.01
- Ewen, Sam Travis
  - [Untitled], 0633; 301; Stickers that were posted all around the 5 boroughs starting September 18. 4 of 6 "WTC. 09. 11. 01"
- Ewen, Sam Travis
  - [Untitled], 0634; 302; Stickers that were posted all around the 5 boroughs starting September 18. 5 of 6 "09.11.01"
- Ewen, Sam Travis
  - [Untitled], 0635; 303; Stickers that were posted all around the 5 boroughs starting September 18. 6 of 6 image of wtc towers in star
- Ewen, Stuart
  - [Untitled], 0636; 294; By nome de plume, Archie Bishop, cash register, let freedom ring
- Faccinto, Victor
  - [Untitled], 0637; 108; Artwork via mail
- Factor 44
  - [Untitled], 0638; 1833; 1832-1841; sketched animals
- Factor 44
  - [Untitled], 0639; 1832; 1832-1841; who benefits
- Factor 44
  - [Untitled], 0640; 1834; 1832-1841; lines
- Factor 44
  - [Untitled], 0641; 1835; 1832-1841; text
- Factor 44
  - [Untitled], 0642; 1836; 1832-1841; rood
- Factor 44
  - [Untitled], 0643; 1837; 1832-1841; tin jacobs
- Factor 44
  - [Untitled], 0644; 1838; 1832-1841; WTC w/crescents
- Factor 44
  - [Untitled], 0645; 1839; 1832-1841; atheist
- Factor 44
  - [Untitled], 0646; 1840; 1832-1841; Your cat did it
- Fales, Jamie
  - [Untitled], Hand print; 0648; 1581
- Fales, Jamie
  - [Untitled], 0649; 1580; Drips
- Farinacci, Paul
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0650; 1452
- Farooq, Hassan
  - Beginning til the end, 0652; 3002
- Farsad, Sarah & Wager, Richard
  - The contribution of the artist in society post 9-11, 0653; 593
- Calik, Gilsen
  - [Untitled], 0654; 1764; Two band-aids
- Fausti, Eduardo
  - [Untitled], 0655; 1607; White flower in center
- Fee, Mariah
  - [Untitled], 0656; 1441; "A sense of uncertainty"
- Feinstein, Emily
  - Random Thoughts, digital image; 0657; 1587
- Feldman, Ronald
  - From the Desk of, 0658; 730
- Felshin, Nina
  - [Untitled], text; 0658b; 3212; Oy to the world
- Fend, Peter
  - Work Now for Independence..., text on paper; 0659; 1569; 3 blocks of large black text down center of page
- Fend, Peter
  - Work Now for Independence from Big Oil, text on paper; 0660; 1570; Block of large black text in center of page
- Fend, Peter
  - Work Now for Independence from Oil and Gas Globally, text on paper; 0661; 1571; Block of large black text in center of page
- Fend, Peter
  - Work Now for Independence from Oil and Gas Industry, text on paper; 0662; 1572; Block of large black text in center of page
- Fennell, Eric
  - [Untitled], 0663; 966; WTC with RIP street sign
- Fernald, Cynthia & Steven
  - [Untitled], 0664; 375; Micah, Tanner, Cynthia & Steven
- Fernald, Cynthia & Steven
  - [Untitled], 0665; 376; Micah, Tanner, Cynthia & Steven
- Fernandez, Fabio
  - Untitled, 0666; 652; USPS envelope
- Ferrante, Michael
  - [Untitled], 0667; 875
- Ferrari, Leon
  - Terrorismos, photocollage; 0668; 955
- Ferrari, Leon
  - [Untitled], 0669; 1008; Sent via e-mail. Image of Jesus crucified on an airplane
- Ferrara-Balanquet, Raul
  - [Untitled], 0670; 2113; Text in Spanish and English bordered by photographic images
- Ferry, Helen
  - Ground Zero, 0671; 2091; Circle within a circle w/a horizontal line
- Feuer, Ejlat
  - [Untitled], 0672; 429; Tallies
- Fidelis, Gaudencio
  - The Sensibility of Absence, cut out of black paper; 0673; 648
- Fierens, Luc
  - [Untitled], 0674; 2198; I remember... 1 of 2
- Fierens, Luc
  - [Untitled], color xerox; 0675; 2199; DEAL! 2 of 2
- Fillmore, Ed
  - Shedding Skin, 0676; 2284; Image of kneeling man shedding skin
- Finberg, Kent
  - Art Journal (Entry Made 7:30 AM September 11, 2001), 0677; 1562; Black text over image
- Fink, David G.
  - [Untitled], 0678; 919
- Fink, Hannah
  - [Untitled], 0679; 651; Wavy
- Finkbeiner, Amy
  - [Untitled], 0680; 792
- Finkel, Alan
  - Liberty Sanctuary Memorial, 0681; 771; Concept: Channel Hudson River water to continually cleanse the site
- Firestone, R.W.
  - Brethren, 0682; 400; Man w/hands on head
- Firestone, R.W.
  - Brethren, 0683; 401; Profile of man
- First, David
  - Jump Back, song; 0684; 3098; Pink sheet with lyrics
- Fisher, Jon
  - Missing, 0686; 3094; Paint and towers
- Fisher, Simon
  - Sifi, 0687; 1197; WTC exploding
- Fleming, Sherman
  - [Untitled], comp art; 0687b; 3226
- Fletcher, Leland
  - [Untitled], 0688; 2274; This page is blank on purpose...
- Flexer, Roland
  - [Untitled], 0689; 680; Web page with devil in smoke image
- Flom, Stephanie
  - Spirit Ascension, JPEG photo of cut paper on plaster wall; 0690; 134
- Flores, Gilbert
  - [Untitled], 0691; 222
- Flower, Matthew
  - Your Hand Here, 0692; 2012
- Flower, Matthew
  - Anarchy in High Heels, 0693; 2011; Twin towers on lined paper and text
- Fly.2K1
  - [Untitled], 0694; 3000; Flag mask w/text
- Fly.2K1
  - [Untitled], 0695; 3001; New York is a beautiful city full of...
- Folan, Ryan
  - September 11th's Lessons to US, 0697; 1688; "They are a nation..."
- Folan, Ryan
  - [Untitled], 0702; 1693; Hands and tower
- Fonde, Carol
  - Understanding September 11th, poem; 0703; 2177
- Ford, Robin
  - [Untitled], photograph; 0704; 1798; Photo of ground zero
- Ford, Ted C. & Mathey, Carol
  - [Untitled], digital collages; 0705; 631; "Gulpin' gargoyles, Harry..."
- Ford, Ted C. & Mathey, Carol
  - [Untitled], digital collages; 0706; 630; TV show collages
- Ford-Aikin, Dierdre
  - [Untitled], ink, chalk, pencil; 0707; 931; Buy American in towers
- Forrest, Elaine
  - [Untitled], 0708; 344; Collage with Cantor Fitz. Fax
- Fort Washington Shelter/Erasmo Velez
  - [Untitled], 0709; 2237; Graffiti
- Fort Washington Shelter/Martin Rodriguez
  - [Untitled], 0710; 2238; Geometry
- Fort Washington Shelter/C.P.
  - [Untitled], 0711; 2239; Satellite
- Fort Washington Shelter/Shawn Luzaki
  - [Untitled], 0712; 2240; Flowers
- Fort Washington Shelter/Eddie Williams
  - [Untitled], 0713; 2241; Perseus
- Fort Washington Shelter/Robert Scott
  - [Untitled], 0714; 2242; Portrait
- Fort Washington Shelter/Rojas
  - [Untitled], 0715; 2243; Guilty
- Fort Washington Shelter/Rojas
  - [Untitled], 0716; 2244; Guilty
- Fort Washington Shelter/Alexandra Rojas
  - [Untitled], 0717; 2245; Resent
- Fort Washington Shelter/Castrucci
  - [Untitled], 0718; 2246; Gone
- Fort Washington Shelter/Castrucci
  - [Untitled], 0719; 2247; Gone
- Fort Washington Shelter/Melvia Way Castrucci
  - [Untitled], 0720; 2248; Copote
- Fort Washington Shelter/Castrucci & Perez
  - [Untitled], 0721; 2249; Bust
- Fort Washington Shelter/Castrucci
  - [Untitled], 0723; 2251; Gone
- Fort Washington Shelter/Castrucci
  - [Untitled], 0724; 2252; Gone
- Fort Washington Shelter/Castrucci
  - [Untitled], 0725; 2253; U.S.A.R.I.P. not
- Fort Washington Shelter/Castrucci
  - [Untitled], 0726; 2254; Gone
- Fort Washington Shelter
  - [Untitled], 0727; 2255; Rico
- Foster, Emrie Brooke
  - Shish Shawnye, oil/acrylic; 0728; 1514
- Fouhy, Brian
  - [Untitled], 0730; 1756; Statue of liberty w/gas mask
- Fouhy, Brian
  - [Untitled], 0731; 1758; Bulls eye
- Foust, Marta
  - [Untitled], poster; 0732; 973; 1 of 3
- Foust, Marta
  - [Untitled], poster; 0733; 974; 2 of 3
- Foust, Marta
  - [Untitled], poster; 0734; 975; 3 of 3
- Fowler, Bruce
  - [Untitled], 0735a; 121; 1 of 2 photograph via mail
- Fowler, Bruce
  - [Untitled], photograph; 0735b; 121; 2 of 2 photograph via mail
- Fowler, Bruce
  - [Untitled], 0736; 122; 2 of 2 photographs of installation piece, via mail
- Frain, Rose
  - [Untitled], 0738; 3013; Via email
- Frain, Rose
  - [Untitled], 0739; 3014; Via email
- Franc, Neal
  - [Untitled], 0740; 353; Everything Stands Still photo with powerline image
- Francia, Luis
  - [Untitled], 0741; 2151
- Frankel, Larry S.
  - [Untitled], photograph; 0743; 87; By mail
- Frasconi, A.
  - [Untitled], 0744; 912; Lino cut and cut out collage
- Fraser, Diane
  - New Eyes, poem; 0744b; 2149; History repeating itself...
- Freed, Ken
  - [Untitled], 0745; 36; Text via email
- Freedman, Marcy B.
  - Going, going, gone, lipstick kisses; 0746; 288
- Freeland, Tessa Hughes
  - [Untitled], 0747; 1126; I was overcome by anxiety...
- French, MC
  - Chabers Light, pinhole photograph; 0748; 642; Diamond shape
- Freygang, Katherine
  - The Clear Self, poem; 0749; 3059
- Fridman, Paulo
  - Douglas Wants to be a Policeman, San Paulo, Brazil, 0750; 1940; Black child w/writing over it
- Fridman, Paulo
  - Patricia e Rose Olho por olho, dente por dente, e o mundo acabara cego e banquela, photograph; 0751; 1941; Patricia and Rose, San Paulo, Brazil. Two girls w/Portuguese writing
- Fried, Clay
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0752; 1262; One broad light vertical stripe bordered by two broad dark stripes
- Friedemann, Nancy
  - Tora Bora/ Gerhard Richter, newspaper with vellum; 0753; 810
- Friederichs, Friederun
  - Threads of hope, photocopy of signs and letters from all over the world and times on woven f; 0754; 518; Paper collage
- Friedetzky, Claudia
  - [Untitled], laser print block; 0755; 884; We couldn't be prouder
- Friedman, Barbara
  - [Untitled], laser print; 0756; 486; Bedroom interior
- Friedman, Charley
  - [Untitled], marker on velium; 0757; 785; The words "Thank You" written in English and Arabic
- Frohman, Doug
  - [Untitled], 0758; 1440; David Garcia
- Frontero, Gisella
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0759; 2092; Light splatters on dark background
- Fry, David
  - One=Infinity, 0760; 1697; Sheets of paper
- Funtenrose, Marilyn
  - [Untitled], digital image photoshop; 0761; 1827; People's cover with Osama on it
- Furman, Wendy
  - Rorschach, 0762; 281
- G., Paul
  - [Untitled], 0763; 2040; Barbed wire
- Gaddy, Raymond W.
  - [Untitled], 0765; 1123; Dragonfly
- Galindo, Felipe
  - Day of the Dead Altar for the Victims of 9-11, 0766; 716
- Galvao, Leonardo
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0769; 2075; Image of Windows computer screen w/text: "others"
- Gamble, Jeff
  - [Untitled], 0770; 3009; 4-page account, starts "The sirens that howl..."
- Gamble, Jeff
  - [Untitled], 0771; 3010; 4-page account, starts "The sirens that howl..."
- Gamble, Jeff
  - [Untitled], 0772; 3011; 4-page account, starts "The sirens that howl..."
- Gamble, Jeff
  - [Untitled], 0773; 3012; 4-page account, starts "The sirens that howl..."
- Gang, Jane
  - [Untitled], 0774; 1124; Pussy cat lounge
- Gruen, Alex
  - [Untitled], 0775; 1352; Close-up of Jackie Kennedy
- Gannis, Carla
  - Forlorn Imagination, 0776; 1995
- Gantman, Martin
  - [Untitled], photocopy; 0778; 25; Postcard copied on both sides--sent via mail
- Ganz, Beth
  - September 13 - Union Square, phtogravure with ChineColle; 0779; 2236; Candles
- Garcia, Ines
  - [Untitled], color photo; 0779b; 3208; Cohete
- Gardner, Donald
  - The Glittering Sea, 0780; 3075
- Garet, Richard
  - [Untitled], watercolor drawing; 0781; 356
- Garnetty, J.
  - Cluster, epson print; 0782; 1054
- Garofalo, Gabriela y Jose
  - [Untitled], 0783; 2287
- Gast, Tory
  - [Untitled], 0784; 606; Airplane 1 of 2
- Gast, Tory
  - [Untitled], 0785; 605; Crows 2 of 2
- Gay, Dixie Friend
  - Shadows of Truth, 0786; 1956; Women w/no faces
- Gay, Dixie Friend
  - [Untitled], 0787; 3016; Via email
- Gazinelli, Deley
  - [Untitled], 0788; 1010; Black paper with white cursive text along top and right side
- Gecko
  - 9-11, text; 0788b; 3232
- Gee
  - Piece of Peace, 0789; 200; Braille card
- Gee
  - Cap Guns, poem; 0789b; 200b; When we were kids...
- Geirsdottir, Kristin
  - ICELAND Nov. 2001, oil on paper, fier; 0790; 496; Red square
- Geirsdottir, Kristin
  - [Untitled], oil on paper, fier; 0791; 495; Whole sheet
- Gejer, Teresa
  - [Untitled], 0792; 749
- Gelenian-Wood, Terri
  - 10048, plastic stencilover paper; 0793; 1019; Image of NYC skyline with a green plastic stencil of twin towers over on top of image
- Caraval, George Vincent & Drapala, Pam
  - [Untitled], various poems; 0795; 2154; 1 of 7 poems
- Caraval, George Vincent & Drapala, Pam
  - [Untitled], various poems; 0796; 2155; 2 of 7 poems
- Caraval, George Vincent & Drapala, Pam
  - [Untitled], various poems; 0797; 2156; 3 of 7 poems
- Caraval, George Vincent & Drapala, Pam
  - [Untitled], various poems; 0798; 2157; 4 of 7 poems
- Caraval, George Vincent & Drapala, Pam
  - [Untitled], various poems; 0799; 2158; 5 of 7 poems
- Caraval, George Vincent & Drapala, Pam
  - [Untitled], various poems; 0800; 2159; 6 of 7 poems
- Gerard, Michael
  - [Untitled], 0801; 388; Gorilla
- Gerber, Ava Jo
  - U.S. History, drawing with text; 0802; 780; Poem with drawings
- Giardina, Ed
  - [Untitled], digital print; 0803; 514; Blurry face
- Gibbs, Shanise
  - [Untitled], 0804; 550; 9 of 16
- Gingerich, Tanya Alina
  - [Untitled], text; 0804b; 3231
- Ginsburg, Eric
  - [Untitled], 0805; 85; Artwork via mail
- Gislason, Gylfi
  - [Untitled], print out; 0805b; 3265
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text; 0805c; 1193
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text; 0805d; 1268
- Giordano, Claudia
  - per che?, color printout; 0805e; 1269
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805f; 1270
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805g; 1276
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805h; 1288
- Giordano, Claudia
  - Art, text; 0805i; 3288; Isata Bah
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805j; 3289; This day will never be forgotten
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805k; 1293; Alex Jaquez
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text; 0805l; 1296; Peace love and war
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805m; 1297; Tower plane fire
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text; 0805n; 1298; Jasmine Espinal
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805o; 1299; John Ortiz
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805p; 1300; Carlos Rodriguez
- Giordano, Claudia
  - A day of pain, drawing; 0805q; 1301; Maria Carrasquillo
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805r; 1302; Ayesha Williams
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805s; 1303; Before and after JK
- Giordano, Claudia
  - That Day..., drawing; 0805t; 1304; Jennifer Stevenson
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805u; 1305; Maria Alers
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805v; 1306; Clara O.
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text; 0805w; 1308; Wander Falette
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text; 0805x; 1309; What's going on? Why must we suffer?
- Giordano, Claudia
  - Rest in Peace, drawing; 0805y; 1311; Ettosam Samtasko
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text; 0805z; 1312; Christina Veney
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text and drawing; 0805aa; 1314; Amanda Estrella
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text and drawing; 0805bb; 1316; These Colors don't run
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text and drawing; 0805cc; 1319; Abner L. Mercado
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text and drawing; 0805dd; 1320; Tanice Small
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text and drawing; 0805ee; 1325; Jay Javed Ethendge
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text; 0805ff; 1326; Nefertede Sterling
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805gg; 1328; Eduardo Agusto
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text; 0805hh; 1330; Jessica Garcia
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805ii; 1336; Always united
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text; 0805jj; 1349; Migiul Yami
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text and photo; 0805kk; 1347; Stephaine Bower
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text; 0805ll; 1351; Jeremiah Rodrigues
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], text; 0805mm; 1353; Jaralyn
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805nn; 1359; Peter Vazquez
- Giordano, Claudia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0805oo; 1360; Kaleem Thomas
- Glackin, David
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0806; 1604; The word "void" repeatedly written in a spiral pattern
- Gladman, Randy D.
  - [Untitled], 0807; 5; Submitted letter via email
- Glautzman
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0809; 645
- Glazer, Ronit
  - [Untitled], 0810; 1146; Fragile
- Gleason, Gerry
  - [Untitled], 0811; 242
- Gleaves, Richard
  - [Untitled], 0813; 1934
- Greenfield, Amy
  - from "We Too Are Alive: Poems After and Before 9/11/01", 0814; 673; By Amy Greenfield
- Glen, Niki
  - Rain of Terror, 0815; 1865
- Gober, Bob
  - [Untitled], 0817; 343; Text with drawing dated 11/27/01
- Goddard, Steve
  - [Untitled], photograph; 0818; 945; Flags in store
- Godin, Ginevra
  - infinite chain reaction, digital image; 0819; 1006
- Godoe, Don
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0820; 766; Image of a face in the center with text written around the border
- Goetz, Monika
  - [Untitled], 0821; 1859
- Golbert, Jonathan
  - Chi Erica, crayon and marker on paper; 0821b; 3227
- Goldberg, Elise
  - [Untitled], 0822; 891; Collage with map
- Goldberg, Nicolas
  - [Untitled], 0823; 687; Walking by towers at night
- Goldman, Ben
  - Target, oil on canvas 34" x 58"; 0824; 726
- Goldman, Charles
  - [Untitled], 0825; 19; Dropped off in person --2 mounted photos of public sculpture
- Goldner, Janet
  - [Untitled], photos; 0826; 322; From the 55th floor, north tower, 1993
- Goldsmith, Silvianna
  - Donde Estan? Desaparecidos., 0827; 103; Artwork
- Goldsmith, Gail
  - A Space in Time, 0828; 963
- Goldsmith, Layne
  - [Untitled], 0829; 3020; Via email
- Goldstein, Audrey
  - breathing aid for those who can't breathe, mixed media on paper; 0830; 459
- Goldstein, Deborah
  - [Untitled], 0831; 1770; "my houseguest from japan..."
- Goltesfeld, Linda
  - [Untitled], 0832; 2203; Trees 1 of 2
- Goltesfeld, Linda
  - [Untitled], 0833; 2204; Trees and house 2 of 2
- Gomez, Gabriel
  - [Untitled], 0834; 211; Part of group from students of the Hudson School, "Glory and Pride"
- Gonzalez, Constanza
  - [Untitled], color print; 0834b; 3235
- Gonzalez, Danielle
  - [Untitled], 0835; 208; Part of group from students of the Hudson School
- Gonzalez-Blue, Maria
  - Prayer, chalk pastel; 0837; 1867; Woman w/hands raised and flames
- Gonzalez-Blue, Maria
  - Heart of Ice and Stone, 0838; 1868; Poem
- Goodfriend, Tali
  - "Peace Setting", digital photo; 0839; 1076; Photo of a table setting of pottery dishes
- Goodfriend, Tali
  - "Peace Setting", digital photo; 0840; 1077; Close-up photo of table setting of pottery dishes
- Goodman, Johanna
  - [Untitled], 0841; 2001; Girl w/gas mask
- Goodwin, Claude
  - To-morrow, mixed media; 0842; 1027; Twin towers with heart between them
- Goodwin, Matthew
  - Fancies of Flight, digital image; 0843; 2071; Flag
- Gookin, Kirby & Kahn, Robin
  - [Untitled], 0844; 662; "We're all one blood"
- Gora-Wita, Jolanta
  - Visual Dialogue JG3VD2, drawing (digital print); 0845; 1439; USS Cole
- Gordon, Coco
  - Teach Mayor Bloomberg Permaculture CrashCourse, digital image; 0846; 1815; Two assemblings
- Gordon, Ilse
  - Views of the Manhattan Skyline from Greenwich Point, Two reproductions of paintings; 0847; 1566; Arranged vertically on left side of page with titles on right
- Gordon, Janice
  - Who Will Be Left..?, 0848; 1192; Afghan women
- Gordon, K.
  - [Untitled], 0849; 1339; "Hijackers' meticulous..."